https://inacs.org/links/privacy-policy/

Contact
Privacy Policy for http://inacs.org.
What personal data we collect and why we collect it
Comments
When visitors leave comments on the site we collect the data shown in the comments form, and also the visitor’s IP address and browser user agent string to help spam detection.
An anonymized string created from your email address (also called a hash) may be provided to the Gravatar service to see if you are using it. The Gravatar service privacy policy is available here: https://automattic.com/privacy/. After approval of your comment, your profile picture is visible to the public in the context of your comment.
Media
If you upload images to the website, you should avoid uploading images with embedded location data (EXIF GPS) included. Visitors to the website can download and extract any location data from images on the website.
Contact forms
Cookies
If you leave a comment on our site you may opt-in to saving your name, email address and website in cookies. These are for your convenience so that you do not have to fill in your details again when you leave another comment. These cookies will last for one year.
If you have an account and you log in to this site, we will set a temporary cookie to determine if your browser accepts cookies. This cookie contains no personal data and is discarded when you close your browser.
When you log in, we will also set up several cookies to save your login information and your screen display choices. Login cookies last for two days, and screen options cookies last for a year. If you select “Remember Me”, your login will persist for two weeks. If you log out of your account, the login cookies will be removed.
If you edit or publish an article, an additional cookie will be saved in your browser. This cookie includes no personal data and simply indicates the post ID of the article you just edited. It expires after 1 day.
Embedded content from other websites
Articles on this site may include embedded content (e.g. videos, images, articles, etc.). Embedded content from other websites behaves in the exact same way as if the visitor has visited the other website.
These websites may collect data about you, use cookies, embed additional third-party tracking, and monitor your interaction with that embedded content, including tracking your interaction with the embedded content if you have an account and are logged in to that website.
Analytics
Who we share your data with
How long we retain your data
If you leave a comment, the comment and its metadata are retained indefinitely. This is so we can recognize and approve any follow-up comments automatically instead of holding them in a moderation queue.
For users that register on our website (if any), we also store the personal information they provide in their user profile. All users can see, edit, or delete their personal information at any time (except they cannot change their username). Website administrators can also see and edit that information.
What rights you have over your data
If you have an account on this site, or have left comments, you can request to receive an exported file of the personal data we hold about you, including any data you have provided to us. You can also request that we erase any personal data we hold about you. This does not include any data we are obliged to keep for administrative, legal, or security purposes.
Where we send your data
Visitor comments may be checked through an automated spam detection service.
When you donate to us through Paypal, you will be re-directed to Paypal’s website and subject to their terms and privacy agreement.
What third parties we send data to:
When you donate to us through Paypal, you will be re-directed to Paypal’s website and subject to their terms and privacy agreement.
What automated decision making and/or profiling we do with user data: None.
Industry regulatory disclosure requirements: N/A
Meeting Time & Location
RSVP now at our Meetup Group!
Enter your email address to receive notifications of upcoming Events.
Join 54 other subscribers
Email Address
Donate now with PayPal
Donate through Amazon Donate to INACS every time you make a purchase on Amazon!
CategoriesCategories
Select Category
Archives  (2)
Austin  (7)
BioFeedback  (2)
Consciousness  (24)
Electromagnetics  (1)
EMF  (1)
Events  (75)
NeuroNews  (6)
News  (4)
Parapsychology  (7)
Podcast  (5)
Reality  (2)
Research  (4)
Typology  (1)
Video  (5)
Archives Archives
Select Month
March 2020  (1)
December 2019  (1)
December 2018  (1)
May 2018  (1)
November 2017  (1)
October 2017  (1)
June 2017  (1)
May 2017  (1)
April 2017  (1)
March 2017  (1)
February 2017  (1)
November 2016  (1)
October 2016  (1)
September 2016  (1)
May 2016  (1)
April 2016  (1)
January 2016  (1)
November 2015  (1)
October 2015  (1)
September 2015  (1)
June 2015  (1)
April 2015  (1)
March 2015  (1)
February 2015  (1)
January 2015  (1)
November 2014  (2)
October 2014  (1)
September 2014  (1)
June 2014  (1)
May 2014  (2)
March 2014  (3)
February 2014  (1)
January 2014  (1)
December 2013  (1)
November 2013  (1)
September 2013  (2)
July 2013  (1)
June 2013  (1)
April 2013  (2)
March 2013  (1)
February 2013  (1)
January 2013  (1)
November 2012  (1)
July 2012  (1)
June 2012  (1)
March 2012  (1)
February 2012  (1)
January 2012  (1)
October 2011  (1)
September 2011  (1)
June 2011  (1)
May 2011  (1)
April 2011  (1)
February 2011  (1)
December 2010  (1)
November 2010  (1)
October 2010  (1)
July 2010  (1)
June 2010  (1)
May 2010  (2)
March 2010  (1)
January 2010  (1)
December 2009  (1)
July 2009  (2)
April 2009  (2)
March 2009  (1)
February 2009  (1)
November 2008  (1)
August 2007  (2)
June 2007  (1)
July 2006  (1)
September 2005  (1)
April 2001  (1)
March 2001  (1)
